So before we start the message we might want to get a little bit of oil and again in this case I have grape seed oil, and I'm going to get a little bit, get a little bit oily because we're working on the face and the ears, and the neck, only a tiny bit.
You can always add more but we don't want to put a lot of oil on her face but we do need a little bit because we will be working on some of the neck muscles, we need that gliding motion which oil can help provide.
So I add oil to my hands and I'm warming them up.
Warming them up weather I'm using oil or not so warming it up with oil.
How's that smell, does it smell o.k.?
Yeah, shouldn't have a lot of smell at all.
So Natalie's just probably smelling my hands.
So warming up the oil and I'm going to double check in with you before I even touch you at all.
Is it o.k.
if I give you a message with oil?
O.k.
want to check in and if you're not sure, if you get oil and you've had it for a little bit of time, please smell it first.
If it smells a little unusual, throw it away and get more.
Now you definitely do not want to put oil on a child that might be a little bit rancid, a little bit tainted at all.
It's very inexpensive, just throw it away if you're unsure and get more.
And just again put a little bit of oil, you can always add more and warming your hands before you actually make contact through touch.